忘了它，失败者
Forget it, loser.
哦，伦巴多先生
Oh, Mr. Lombardo.
-嗨. -嗨，朋友
-Hey. -Hey, bro.
伦巴多先生，怎样?
Mr. Lombardo, what's up?
-嘿，朋友. -嘿
-Hey, man. -Hey.
詹尼弗
Jennifer--
你看他的眼睛?
Did you see his eyes?
你在看什么，哦?
What are you looking at, dork?
滚开
Fuck off.
我感激这些家伙来这里
l appreciate you guys coming down.
我在这个垃圾堆里唯一想要的是-
The only thing l'm gonna miss in this dump is....
安静
Settle down.
好吧，我们的高年级研修班课程已经上到一半
Well, we've come to the halfway point of our senior seminars.
安静. 安静
Settle down. Settle down.
- 比自修课还乱，是不是? - 不是!
-Beats study hall, doesn't it? -No!
-是你吉米? -至少在自修室还可以思考
-That you, Jimmy? -At least in study hall l can meditate.
他的意思是可以在这里手淫.'
What he means is, ''masturbate.''
我相信你在这方面一定很有经验，天那
Something with which l'm sure you've had hands-on experience, Kirk.
我没有先生. 我没有
lt wasn't me, man. lt wasn't me.
我是纯洁的. 我是纯洁的
l'm innocent. l'm innocent.
我们都听到过“约会强奸”“性骚扰”这种讲法
We've all heard the terms ''date rape,'' ''sexual harassment.''
就在这里我们也讨论过类似问题
We've discussed some of these issues right here in this very room.
我们今天的客人来自蓝湾警察局
Our guests today come from the Blue Bay Police Department.
警探 杜奎特 和 皮里…
Detectives Duquette and Perez...
…给我们带来一点关于这个专题的大家需要的新看法
...are here to give us what we hope...
...will be a fresh perspective on the subject...
还有…准备回答你们任何人的任何问题
...and to address any questions that any of you might have.
大家热烈欢迎
Now, let's give them a warm welcome.
-多谢. -我要走了
-Thank you. -l'm out of here.
-为何不先问个问题呢?. -问你妈个头
-Why don't we begin with a question. -This prick can kiss my ass.
我刚刚说到…
As l was saying...
…我们为何不从一个问题开始
...why don't we begin with a question.
-什么是性犯罪? -没插进去!
-What is a sex crime? -Not getting any.
怎么了? 那个中途退场的女孩是谁?
What's with that? She's the one who walked out.
-苏西・托乐. -我去年抓过她
-Suzie Toller. -l busted her last year for possession.
可怜的孩子坐了6个月的监
Poor kid did six months in Camp Nine.
-六个月?第一次? -我不太理解这个判决
-Six months? First offense? -l didn't hand down the sentence.
他手脚不干净 我抓过她
She was dirty. l busted her.
嘿，卡罗尔
Hey, Carol.
我很感激你们，小伙子们. 谢谢
l appreciate you guys taking the time to come.
十分乐意
Our pleasure.
为什么感觉您像个教导顾问?
Why do l get the feeling you don't like the guidance counselor?
别告诉我你看不到他以往的表现. 他是只猎犬
Don't tell me you can't see through his routine. He's a total hound.
你说宠物狗?
You mean pussy hound?
实际上，我想他是逗人发笑的那种
Actually, l thought he was kind of cute.
我会做了他
l'd do him.
抓住
Steady.
吉米 抓住船头
Steady the bow, Jimmy.
很好
That's good.
降下主帆
Drop the main.
好吧 各位 收好索具. 大家周一见
All right, guys, let's de-rig and l'll see you all Monday.
嘿，小姐们，我需要洗车
Hey, ladies, my car needs a wash.
窗户呢?
Do you do windows?
大伙儿干的好. 周一见
Good work, guys. A.C., see you Monday.
-再见，伦巴多先生. -好的，巴迪
-See you, Mr. Lombardo. -All right, buddy.
好
All right.
真大，可以在上头开派对
l could definitely party on one of those.
它是小摩托，吉米
lt's a stinkpot, Jimmy.
想做船老大 得搞那个玩意
You wanna be a real boatman, you wanna get yourself one of those.
是
Yeah.
那是一艘真正的船
That's a real boat.
谢谢你让我进这个班
Thank you for getting me into this class.
我家老头绝对不肯付这个钱的
No way my old man was gonna spring for the fees.
你干活挣的 而且你也在摆弄船
Hey, you're working for it, and you're learning your way around a boat.
我也是在船上干活挣够大学学费的
l put myself through college working on boats.
- 胜过腻味的汉堡 - 哈哈是啊
-Beats flipping burgers. -Yeah.
我也可以玩玩?还是只有男孩可以?
Can l play too, or is it just for boys?
那周末谁帮你洗车? 伦巴多先生?
So who's washing your Jeep this weekend, Mr. Lombardo?
高年级洗车会，记不记得?
The senior car wash, remember?
洗我那辆老吉普是浪费时间
Washing that old Jeep of mine is a waste of time.
不会的，让尼科尔和我一起干怎么样
Not at all. How about if Nicole and l do it?
我们合作的很不错
We're working as a team.
那就这样.我星期六到沼林去
l tell you what. l'm going out to the glades Saturday.
为何不周日来?把所有泥巴洗干净
Why don't you come over Sunday and wash all the mud off.
成交
Deal.
我指望着妈妈来带我，但是她没来
l was counting on my mom to give me a ride, but she's not here.
奇怪 奇怪
Surprise, surprise.
所以我在想你能不能带我一段路
So l was wondering if you could give me one.
伦巴多先生，你总不会让我走路吧
Mr. Lombardo, you really wouldn't want me to walk, would you?
我意思是，我不会这么倒霉的吧
l mean, like, something bad might happen.
-你呢 ?需要带一程么? -是的，但我得加上自行车
-What about you, you need a lift? -Yeah, but l got my bike.
没问题
Hey, no problem.
好，来试试
Okay, try it.
苏西，你需要么? 还有一个空位
Suzie, you need a lift? We got room for one more.
天啊. 她哪里弄的鞋子，像个鸡
Jesus. Where'd she get those shoes, ''Whores 4 Less''?
再试试
Try it again.
很高兴见到你走啦孩子们
Nice to see you kids getting along.
-别忘了礼拜日的事情. -不会的
-Don't forget Sunday. -l won't.
-是萨姆 伦巴多么? -嗨，妈妈
-ls that Sam Lombardo? -Hi, Mom.
萨姆，嗨
Sam, hi.
嗨，桑德拉
Hi, Sandra.
进来喝一杯怎样?
Why don't you come on in and have a drink.
不好意思，桑德拉，我得走了
Sorry, Sandra, l gotta run.
-嗨，伦巴多先生. -嗨，伦巴多先生
-Hi, Mr. Lombardo. -Hi, Mr. Lombardo.
嗨，小姐们
Hi, girls.
看吧，我就知道他忘了
Look. He forgot.
我没忘记看车吧
-l knew it. -No, l didn't.
都准备好啦搞得真脏
Check out my Jeep. Nice and dirty for you.
不如等另一辆开走再干
But you might wanna wait till the other car leaves.
那奔驰不是你的?
You mean the Mercedes isn't yours too?
你知道我的那部是蓝的，尼科尔
My Benz is blue. You know that, Nicole.
萨姆，我走啦
Sam, l'm leaving.
你的水管呢?伦巴多先生?
So where's your hose, Mr. Lombardo?
凯利，水管在车子前头
The hose, Kelly, is right in front of the Jeep.
凯利 帮你洗吉普车?
Kelly Van Ryan's gonna wash your Jeep?
芭芭拉.只是找个理由
Come on, Barbara. lt's for a good cause.
萨姆真是个慈善家
Sam the philanthropist.
有人说:多干点小事累不着人
Yeah, well, you know what they say: A little hard work never hurt anyone.
好
Okay.
-玩的开心点. -好的
-Have fun at the club. -Okay.
哇
Wow.
看起来和崭新的一样
Looks brand-new.
你忘了什么吗?
Aren't you forgetting something?
你的洗车票要给我们
Your coupon. We gotta have it.
哦，是的.那东西
Oh, yeah, that thing.
-我们为何不?… -规矩就是规矩，伦巴多先生
-Can't we just--? -Rules are rules, Mr. Lombardo.
好的，我找找
Okay, let me look for it.
伦巴多先生，有点晚了
Mr. Lombardo, we're running kind of late.
尼科尔要去曼森家?
How about if Nicole goes on to the Mansons'?
找到他给我骑
You can give me a ride when you find it.
给我几分钟好不好?
No, no, just give me a minute. Okay?
-走吧. -你肯定?
-Go. -Are you sure?
哦，弗兰克. 哦，上帝
Oh, Frankie. Oh, God.
哦，上帝. 哦，上帝
Oh, God! Oh, God!
操!
Goddamn it!
-你好，这是蓝湾高中. -你好
-Hello, this is Blue Bay High School. -Hello.
你的孩子 今天缺席，星期一--
Your son or daughter was absent today, Monday--
天啊!
Jesus H. Christ!
- 什么? 恩? - 哦，没事
-What? -Oh, nothing.
来吧
Come on.
-阿蒂，你抓了条好大的鱼啊. -是条梭鱼
-Art, this is a hell of a fish you caught. -lt's a barracuda.
你有空的时候
lf you weren't so busy chasing booty...
和我一起来打鱼，你可以亲手抓一条
...you'd have come with me and caught one for yourself.
别说你要吃这东西
Don't tell me you're gonna eat this thing.
为啥?
Why not?
这是梭鱼，有毒，毒死你
lt's a barracuda. lt's poisonous. lt'll kill you.
操，我可以对跟你约会的女人说这个
Shit, man, l could say that about most of the girls you date.
桑德拉・范・赖安 电话找 萨姆
Sandra Van Ryan for Sam.
-桑德拉，什么事? -凯利 今天逃课了，萨姆.
-Sandra, what's up? -Kelly skipped school today, Sam.
你听到什么了?
Have you heard anything?
没有
Not a word.
别担心
Never mind.
我找到她了
l found her.
好
Pull!
听着，萨姆，上次真不错
Listen, Sam, it was really good seeing you the other day.
桑德拉，我现在很忙 不如--
Sandra, l'm real busy right now, so--
对我这只船来说没人开得比你好
l haven't found anyone who can handle my boat the way you can.
-是的，好吧-- -我知道你正在操 芭芭拉巴克斯特
-Yeah, well-- -l know you're fucking Barbara Baxter.
-那又怎样? -好吧 也许我只能跟一个女人在一起
-So what? -So maybe l'm a one-woman man now.
可怜的 萨姆.
Aw, poor Sam.
你真想找一个蓝湾女人嫁给你?
Really think you'll get one of these Blue Bay women to marry you?
-讲完啦？桑德拉? -抓住关键，亲爱的.
-Are you finished, Sandra? -Grab a clue, honey.
你是收费的 床上工夫不错 向来不错
You're a hired hand, a good lay. That's as far as it goes.
好好享受吧，趁现在还行
Enjoy it, while it lasts.
再见，桑德拉
Goodbye, Sandra.
放!
Pull!
你似乎把枪当心理医生啦
You seem to find guns therapeutic.
也许我该试一下
Maybe l ought to try it.
好吧，让我来猜猜
So let me guess.
整个周末某个男孩子都没来惹你
Some boy didn't call and screwed up your whole weekend.
白白过一天?对不对?
So you're taking the day off. Right?
那又是你的哪个水手?
Which one of your deck hands is that?
管他哪个，只要是我想要的
Whichever one l want.
好吧，凯利，发生什么事了?
Okay, Kelly, what's the matter?
怎么了?
What is it?
我想爸爸
l miss Dad.
上帝
Jesus.
我也想他，有时候吧
l miss him too, sometimes.
你才不会
No, you don't.
他不应该自杀，凯利
He didn't have to kill himself, Kelly.
哦，凯利…
Oh, Kelly....
我不知道他为什么要这么做
l don't know why he did it.
我真的不知道
l really don't.
我能帮你什么吗?
Can l--?
Can l get you anything?
镇静片?
Do you want a Valium?
我被强奸了
l was raped.
什么，亲爱的? 我没听清楚
-What, honey? l can't hear you. -l said, l was raped.
什么?
What?
我是说，我被强奸了
l was raped...
…被 萨姆 伦巴多强奸了
...by Sam Lombardo.
萨姆 伦巴多?
Sam Lombardo?
我的女儿… 在蓝湾有人敢强奸!
My daughter does not get raped in Blue Bay!
你是说萨姆 伦巴多 强奸了她?
And you're saying that Sam Lombardo raped her?
那个混蛋敢对我女儿做这种事， 一定是在发昏
That son of a bitch must be insane to think he can do this to me.
我们知道您心情，范・赖安夫人…
We understand your feelings, Miss Van Ryan...
…不过 我们还是要先跟 凯利谈下
...but please, we need some time with Kelly.
我们最好记录她的单方陈述
We'd like to take her statement alone.
- 你准备好啦? - 好吧
-Are you all right with this, baby? -Yeah.
好
Okay.
要不要再等一下?
Would you like to take a break for a minute?
我只想快点儿结束
l just wanna get it over with.
我们得录下这些陈诉
We'd like to videotape this statement.
我知道这个不好受，凯利 但这是很严重的指控…
l know this isn't pleasant, Kelly, but these are serious charges...
所以我们要知道你两个之间发生的每一件事
...and we need to know everything that happened between the two of you.
准备好了吗?
Are you ready?
他先是抓住我的肩膀
He started rubbing my shoulders.
我让他--
I let him.
我是说，他的确讨人喜欢…
I mean, he's a nice guy.
然后呢…
The next thing...
他的手在我短裤里--.
...his hand was in my shorts.
这个，从后面.
You know, from behind.
他的手指….
His fingers....
-他的手指… -说清楚…
-His fingers.... -Take your time.
他把手指放进去--.
They were in me.
两个地方，你知道?
Both places, you know?
他进入你的身体了吗?
Did he put himself inside you?
是的.
Yes.
我说“不要.” 我尖叫.
I said ''Stop. '' I screamed.
我头脑一片空白只有这个声音在叫
I mean, that's how it sounded in my head.
他伤害我.
He hurt me.
你反抗过?
Did you try to fight him?
他把我的手腕扭在背后.
Well, he had my wrists pinned behind me.
然后怎样?
Then what?
他一直在说，来吧来吧.
He kept saying, ''Let it happen.
来吧.
Let it happen. ''
然后他突然停下来.
And then he just stopped.
你是说，他离开啦?
You mean he withdrew?
我不知道，很难讲清楚
I don't know. It's really hard to remember, exactly.
尽量想想，凯利.
Try, Kelly.
我只记得他在说 .
I know one thing he said.
他说，“不要怕. 我没有射.”
He said, ''Don't worry. I didn't come. ''
我忘不了那些话.
I can't forget that.
他说:小女孩不能给我高潮.
He said, ''No little girl can ever make me come. ''
小女孩不能给我高潮.  上帝
''No little girl can ever make me come.'' Jesus.
还真坏.我们得搞一点物证
Too bad. We might have had some physical evidence.
怎么了?
What?
也许根本没有物证，因为也许什么都没发生
Maybe there's no physical evidence because nothing happened.
知道我的想法?我觉得她在演戏
You want my gut? There it is. l think she's acting.
我觉得是她找机会跟他单独在一起，希望他能搞点事情
l think she set it up to be alone with him so he'd come on to her.
她很失望 因为他不肯做
She's upset because he didn't.
也许她是那样计划的. 也许不是
Maybe she set it up that way. Maybe not.
那家伙应该让让她站那儿别动
The guy never should've had her there in the first place.
我掌握的情况是，他干过蓝湾半数的女人
The line l have on him, he's done half the women in Blue Bay.
但这个不能把他变成强奸犯
That doesn't make him a rapist.
对她使用测谎仪怎样?
What about asking her to take a polygraph?
让主教大人做个尿检怎样？
What about asking the pope to take a piss test?
这里是蓝湾.，格洛里亚
This is Blue Bay, Gloria.
让范・赖安家的人测谎，汤姆巴克斯特 还不得砍你
Ask a Van Ryan to take a lie detector test and Tom Baxter will cut you down.
你害怕汤姆巴克斯特? 你害怕桑德拉・范・赖安?
You afraid of Tom Baxter now? You afraid of Sandra Van Ryan?
讨论结束，你们俩知道该怎么做
End of discussion. You both know what to do.
调查他的邻居，同事， 再跟凯利的朋友谈谈
Start with his neighbors, coworkers. Talk to Kelly's friends.
-你知道那对他意味着什么. -是的
-You know what that'll mean for him. -Yeah.
你也听到凯利的指控了. 这家伙是混蛋.给我把案卷搞出来
And you heard Kelly's statement. The guy's dirty. Bring me a case.
好
All right.
干得好，纪姆波 星期一见
Good work, Jimbo. l'll see you Monday.
好
All right.
他是我航海课的标兵
That's what's left of my sailing class.
跟我说吧，阿蒂
Talk to me, Artie.
凯利 范・赖安指控你强奸她
Kelly Van Ryan is accusing you of rape.
吉米告诉我的
Jimmy told me.
很显然，我是最后一个知道的
Apparently, l'm the last one to know about it.
萨姆，我…
Sam, l....
桑德拉・范・赖安一整天都在做大喇叭…
Sandra Van Ryan has been on the horn all day...
跟学校当局的每一个人诉说
...with every member of the school board.
她在努力让你停职
She's pushing for suspension.
难道校方只听她的一面之辞，却不听听我的?
And the board's just gonna roll over for her without hearing my side?
真是昏头啦. 我是清白的，该死的
This is insane. l'm innocent, goddamn it.
你要相信我
You gotta believe that.
我能告诉你的就是那事就这样挂着
All l can tell you, Sam, is hang in there.
他们相信你，一切都会恢复照旧的--
They clear you, you get reinstated--
你不明白这种事
You never get clear of something like this.
它会跟着你
lt stays with you.
一直都会跟着你
lt follows you around forever.
你需要有人帮助
You're gonna need some help, Sam.
你需要一位律师
You're gonna need an attorney.
或者你能够告诉我在南佛罗里达还有个律师…
Right. And maybe you can tell me which attorney in South Florida...
想在法庭上和范・赖安家族作对
...is gonna wanna go up against the Van Ryans in court.
我找肯・宝登
l'm here to see Ken Bowden.
-你有预约? -是的
-Do you have an appointment? -Oh, yeah. Sam Lombardo.
好，然后
Okay, then.
好的
Mr. Bowden, your 1 0:30's here.
请带他进来
Will you show him in, please?
是什么事让你跑到城的这头来的?
What brings you to this part of town?
好吧，我呢，直到昨天…
Well, l was, until yesterday...
我还是蓝湾高中的法律辅导员
...a guidance counselor at Blue Bay High School.
那儿的一个学生指控我强奸
A student there is accusing me of rape.
男孩还是女孩?
Male or female?
-那个学生是 凯利・范・赖安 -桑德拉・范・赖安家的?
-The student is Kelly Van Ryan. -As in Sandra Van Ryan?
他妈的.我真够运气
As in, l'm fucked.
说说看?
Why don't you tell me about it?
-从哪儿开始呢? -就从…
-Shit, where do l begin? -Start with...
…你和这个女孩儿的关系说起吧，叫凯利的
...your relationship with the girl, Kelly.
她是我的一个学生.我是她的法律辅导员.除了这个，没有其他关系
She's a student. l was her counselor. Beyond that, there's no relationship.
那就别担心
You got nothing to worry about.
-你把你脖子怎么了? -这个?
-What did you do to your neck? -This?
我不用整天带着这个的
l don't have to wear it all the time.
先前有个保险公司的小子在那儿
There was an insurance guy around here earlier.
好吧，让我先说说费用
All right, let me tell you how l charge.
乔治，你好.跟我说说有啥新闻？
Georgie, hey. We gonna catch some wind?
恐怕今天我不能为你停车了
Mr. Lombardo, l'm afraid l can't park your car today.
你不能为我停车? 我要和芭芭拉一起午餐
You can't park me? l'm meeting Barbara for lunch.
帮我停下车，乔治.我有点儿晚啦
Can you get this parked, Georgie? We're running late.
马上，巴克斯特先生
Right away, Mr. Baxter.
你别上这儿来啦，伦巴多先生. 离这儿远点儿
You're finished here, Lombardo. Take a hike.
芭芭拉，我们走
Barbara, let's go.
也许你没听清我说什么，伦巴多
Maybe you didn't hear me, Lombardo.
你在蓝湾完蛋啦
You're finished in Blue Bay.
如果我再发现你缠着我女儿， 你就彻底完蛋了
l find you around my daughter again, you'll be finished, period.
-滚开吧. - 伦巴多先生，请吧
-Get the fuck out of here. -Mr. Lombardo, please.
那好吧，乔治
That's all right, George.
萨姆，亲爱的. 有一阵子没见你了
Sam, honey. Haven't seen you in a while.
-欢迎回来 -朗姆酒加可乐
-Welcome back. -Rum and Coke.
你还好吗?
Hey! Are you all right?
-我没事. -酷?
-l'm fine. -Cool?
你这个混蛋，他妈的
That's too bad, motherfucker.
萨姆?
Sam?
伦巴多?
Lombardo?
站住，别动!是我啊
Whoa, man! lt's me.
对不起.这事儿越来越古怪了
Sorry, man. Things have been getting a little weird around here.
我明白
l can see that.
进来吧
Come on in.
你确定是 弗兰克・亢多干的?
You're sure this Frankie Condo guy is the guy that did this to you?
就是他，没错
lt was him, all right.
他开着桑德拉的车子
He was driving Sandra's Range Rover.
你把这些告诉警察，我们现在就能逮捕 桑德拉・范・赖安
You tell that to the cops, we can go after Sandra Van Ryan right now.
-这事儿算啦. -这女人很有办法
-Forget it. -The lady has deep pockets.
我知道她多有办法
Believe me, l know how deep her pockets are.
我想过或者我还能保住房子 有些房屋抵押贷款--
l thought l might be able to save my house. Some sort of equity loan.
猜猜谁是银行的部门主管?
Guess who's on the board of directors at the bank?
这个女人够给我添乱的啦
l don't need any more trouble from this woman.
你觉得是不是应该弄个诉讼来让她住手?
You think making some sort of statement's gonna stop her?
你说凯利跟我那件鸟事? 怎么样
With the shit l got on Kelly? Yeah.
一年前…
A year ago...
她父亲把自己脑袋打开花
...when her old man blew his brains out...
…凯利 失魂落魄，离家出走
...Kelly lost it, ran away.
他们在一家破汽车旅馆里找到她时，可卡因正搞得她魂飞天外
They found her in a fleabag motel some place, coked out of her gourd.
这当中--
Meanwhile...
…你，萨姆，在那一年当了辅导员…
...you, Sam, are voted Educator of the Year...
…也许这都是废话
...or some crap.
他们把你们两个推到陪审员前面…
They put the two of you in front of a jury...
…看上去很蠢. 他们知道的
...they're gonna look stupid. They know it.
为什么他们到现在还没来要你的呈述?
Why do you think they haven't taken your statement yet?
因为他们忙于寻找证据…
Because they're busy looking for dirt.
但他们什么也不会发现
And they're not gonna find it.
对不对?
Right?
肯，我没有操我的学生
Ken, l don't fuck my students.
他只是在给你表演一下
He's just showing off for you now.
嘿，那儿，鲁比
Hey there, Ruby.
看来你还是跟沃尔特将就着
l see you still got Walter.
我是希望有什么东西把他吃掉
l was hoping something had eaten him by now.
-有什么事吗? -苏西给我们电话了
-Can l help you with something? -Suzie called us.
她在哪儿?
Where would we find her?
你认得路的
You know the way.
你不会开枪打她吧，啊?
You won't shoot her, will you?
我不相信她会有武装
l don't believe she's armed.
谁呀?
Yeah?
你们路上走这么久
Jesus, it took you guys long enough.
有人来掐死我的话时间刚好够… 或者操我的屁股
What if someone was trying to strangle me or fuck me in the ass?
你们负责性犯罪?
l mean, you guys do sex crimes, right?
我的搭档，皮里警探
My partner, Detective Perez.
这是西林. 他很棒…他对贱人很有研究
lt's Céline. He's okay. He had a good line on what cheap fucks people are.
苏西，你打电话叫我们来.记得吗?
Yeah, so Suzie, you called us. Remember?
他们把伦巴多先生关起来啦?
Did they arrest Mr. Lombardo?
没有
No.
- 会关他? - 我不知道
-Will they? -l don't know.
你操心这个?
That bothers you?
我想出去走走
l wanna go outside.
萨姆 伦巴多让你搭他的便车是什么时候?
When was this that Sam Lombardo gave you the ride?
大概一年前
About a year ago.
你是什么时候到达的，那儿有其他人吗?
And when you arrived at your trailer, was anyone there?
-没有. -这么说只有你一个人
-Nope. -So you were alone.
是
Yeah.
他和你一起进屋了吗?
Did he come in with you?
-我想是. -你想是的.好吧，进还是没有?
-l guess. -You guess. Well, did he or didn't he?
好吧.是，他进屋了
Okay. Yeah, he did.
然后呢?他摸你了吗?
And then what? Did he touch you?
你，也许，有没有跟他调情?
Did you maybe flirt with him a little?
苏西，我知道你很难受
Suzie, look, l know you feel bad.
-但你必须告诉我们实情. -我什么也没跟他说
-Just tell us the truth. -l didn't say a thing to him.
他抱住我说我很好看
He just put his arm around me and told me l was pretty.
他说他想知道我是否真的好看
l could be really pretty, he said.
你有没有要他停下来?
Did you ask him to stop?
见鬼
Shit.
这有什么差别?不管怎样都没人会相信我的
What difference does it make? No one believes me anyway.
-萨姆 伦巴多强奸你了? - 是的. 好不好?他做了
-Did Sam Lombardo rape you? -Yeah. Okay? He did.
他把我推倒在地板上，然后他干了
He pushed me to the floor and he did it to me.
- 那我们算是结束啦？ - 差不多是苏西
-Now are we done? -Almost, Suzie.
差不多
Almost.
这么说吧，你有没有反抗过?
At some point, were you able to fight him off?
没有.他自己停下来了
No. He stopped by himself.
好了吧?就是这些了?让我一个人呆会儿
Okay? ls that it? Leave me alone.
- 别碰我! - 放松点…放松点…
-Don't touch me! -All right, take it easy. Take it easy.
他停下来了
He stopped.
就这些?他就这么离开了?
And that was it? He just left?
是的
Yeah.
他先说过一句话
He did say one thing first.
说什么?
What was that?
他说:“没有小婊子能给我高潮的.”
He said, ''No little bitch can ever make me come.''
打开门
Open the gate.
- 嘿，辅导员，给支烟怎么样? - 你好，倒霉蛋
-Hey, counselor, how about a smoke? -Hello, Jinxy.
现在的消息是好坏各半
You know, it's really a bad news, good news situation.
你不准保释，但你有个真正的律师…
You were denied bail, but you got a real attorney...
而不是由法庭随便指派个辩护人
...instead of a public defender.
我告诉你，肯，我是清白的
l'm telling you, Ken, l'm innocent.
你还是对法庭的人说吧.你不是孤立无援的
You are preaching to the choir. You're not alone.
你就是那个小色鬼
So you're the new chicken licker.
桑德拉，说说你的想法?
Sandra, can we get your comment?
能谈谈你此时的心情吗?
Can l just have your feelings at this time?
伦巴多 先生会得到应有的惩罚的
Mr. Lombardo will get what he deserves.
能说几句话吗?
Can you tell us anything?
- 您有信心打赢这场官司吗? - 很有信心
-Are you confident about the case? -Very. Yes.
伦巴多强奸案在蓝湾高级住宅区引起轰动…
The Lombardo rape case has galvanized the upscale town...
在那些小报的煽动下
...of Blue Bay with its tabloid appeal.
刚刚到达的是，桑德拉・范・赖安…
Now just arriving, Sandra Van Ryan...
大宗地产的女继承人 蓝湾上流社会的精英
...jet-set real estate heiress and part of the powerful Blue Bay elite.
从相反方向过来的是那女孩
And the girl from the wrong side of the tracks. ln the end, the jury...
到最后，陪审团要在这个18岁的女孩…
...must choose between the words of these 1 8-year-old girls...
和萨姆 伦巴多的呈词之间作出裁决
...and that of Sam Lombardo.
这是在法院门前的现场报道… 我是新闻目击栏目的南西・多尔
Reporting from the courthouse steps, l'm Nancy Duerr.
我是新闻目击栏目的南西・多尔
Eyewitness News.
佛罗里达州州对萨姆 伦巴多的起诉.
The State of Florida v. Sam Lombardo.
尊敬的西尔维亚・B・瓦克斯曼法官 全体起立
The Honorable Sylvia B. Waxman presiding. All rise.
我们要站起来
We gotta stand up.
请坐下
Please be seated.
现在坐下
Now sit down.
还要等等，凯利?
Would you like more time, Kelly?
我知道这很难，凯利…
l know that this is hard, Kelly...
但我还要多问一个问题
...but l have one more question.
虽然大部分事实已经陈述过
And even though it's something we've been over...
但我希望我们大家完全弄清楚这件事
...l want us all to be very clear about it.
凯利，当你看到伦巴多先生…
Kelly , when you saw that Mr. Lombardo...
试图和你发生性行为时
...intended to have sex with you...
准确地说 你如何说的?
...what were your exact words?
他说了什么?
What did you say?
我对他说“不要.”
l told him ''No.''
我说，停下来，伦巴多先生.求你了…
l said, ''Stop, Mr. Lombardo. Please.''
我尖叫着要他停下来
l screamed for him to stop.
你尖叫着要他…
You screamed for him...
…停下来
...to stop.
那他呢?
And did he?
不
No.
他在那脏屋子的地板上强奸了我
He raped me on the floor of his shitty house.
谢谢你
Thank you.
这是伦巴多强奸案的第二天…
lt's day two of the Lombardo rape case and the second alleged young victim...
又有第二个前法律辅导员的年轻受害者…
站出来声称
...of the former guidance counselor has taken the stand.
昨天，凯利 范・赖安对事件做了激动的陈述
Yesterday, Kelly Van Ryan delivered an emotional account of events...
…在辩护律师的交叉质询下毫不动摇.
...and was not swayed by defense counsel's cross-examination.
早间晚些时候我们将回到有新的进展的事件现场
We'll come back live later with an update of these proceedings.
法庭门前的现场报道… 我是新闻目击栏目的…
Reporting from the courthouse steps, I'm Nancy Duerr...
南西・多尔
...Eyewitness News.
各位早上好
Good morning, everybody.
托乐小姐
Ms. Toller.
当你…
When you were...
还是蓝湾的新生，因在商店行窃被抓时
...picked up for shoplifting your freshman year at Blue Bay...
你被允许打一个电话…
...and you were allowed to make one call...
你打给伦巴多先生. 是不是这样?
...you called Mr. Lombardo. lsn't that correct?
托乐小姐?
Ms. Toller?
-是. -当你被开除…
-Yes. -And when you were expelled...
…因为毁坏蓝湾高中的财产
...for destruction of school property--
我只是搞坏一个破窗户.那甚至不是我的错
l broke a fucking window. And it wasn't even my fault.
托乐小姐，你要等要求你回答时才能讲话…
Ms. Toller, you will wait until you are asked before responding...
否则你会因为亵渎法庭而受到拘训
...and you will refrain from using profanity in this court.
伦巴多先生出席你的家长会
lt was Mr. Lombardo who appeared with you in lieu of a parent conference.
对吗?
ls that right?
是
Yes.
在我看来…
lt seems to me...
…伦巴多先生是你的朋友
...that Mr. Lombardo was your friend.
他过去是的
He was.
但这一切都改变了，当…
But all that changed when...
…根据你的陈述
...according to your testimony...
伦巴多先生…
...Mr. Lombardo...
…强奸你…
...raped you...
…时间是去年的4月23日，对吗?
...on April 23 of last year, is that right?
- 是. - 但是接着在5月…
-Yes. -But then in May...
…当你因为非法持有毒品被逮捕时…
...when you were arrested for possession of narcotics...
…而再次被允许打一个电话时…
...and again allowed a phone call...
…你又是打给伦巴多先生
...you called Mr. Lombardo.
-那又怎样? -那又怎样?
-So what? -So what?
怎样?
So what?
你看，苏西
Oops, Suzie.
那就是说 在你说的那个男人强奸你的仅仅一个月后，你去向他求助?
So one month after you say this man raped you, you go to him for help?
听起来你仍然觉得伦巴多先生是一个很好的朋友
Sounds as if you still considered Mr. Lombardo a good friend.
- 我需要帮助. - 我知道你需要
-l needed help. -l'm sure you did.
但是伦巴多先生这次不在那里
But Mr. Lombardo wasn't there this time.
那是夏天，他外出了…
lt was summer, he was gone...
你在州立管教所里度过6个月
...and you spent six months in a state correctional facility.
那是不是让你生气啦苏西，苏西…
Did that make you mad, Suzie...
…因为萨姆外出?? 他没在那儿?
...that Sam was gone? That he wasn't there?
就是因为这原因你才这么说 伦巴多先生的?
ls that why you're saying these things about Mr. Lombardo...
-…说你的朋友? -我这么说是因为它发生过
-...your friend? -l said them because they happened.
你能坐在这里，宣誓
Ms. Toller, are you gonna sit there today, under oath...
说塞缪尔・伦巴多强奸你?
...and swear that Samuel Lombardo raped you?
我说过他做了
l said he did.
我来问你一个问题.托乐小姐
Let me ask you a question, Ms. Toller.
你很喜欢做政府的客人对不对?
Did you enjoy being a guest of the state?
因为我敢肯定如果你对山姆伦巴多这事说谎的话…
Because l promise you, if you are lying about this...
而且我相信你说了谎…
...and l believe you are...
你会很快再次光临管教所
...that you will be visiting that facility again quite soon.
那就是为什么我要再次问你…你发誓…
Which is why l'm gonna ask you again now, under oath.
苏西…
Suzie...
…塞缪尔・伦巴多有没有强奸你?
...did Samuel Lombardo rape you?
托乐小姐，你必须回答这个问题
Ms. Toller, you will have to answer the question.
托乐小姐. -去死吧!
-Ms. Toller. -Goddamn it!
- 这不是我的主意. - 反对，法官大人
-This was not my idea. -Objection, Your Honor.
很明显托乐小姐正被律师诱导
Ms. Toller is clearly responding to defense counsel's badgering.
法庭很想听听托勒小姐说的话
Court would like to hear what Ms. Toller has to say.
托乐小姐?
Ms. Toller?
萨姆 伦巴多没有强奸我
Sam Lombardo didn't rape me.
他也没有强奸凯利. 他什么也没做
He didn't rape Kelly either. He didn't do anything.
这真荒谬，证人受到辩护律师的直接恐吓
This is ridiculous. The witness has been threatened by defense counsel!
我已经说明了法庭将要听取托乐小姐的陈诉
l think l made it plain this court intends to hear Ms. Toller's story.
托乐小姐
Ms. Toller.
我想伤害 伦巴多先生
l just wanted to hurt Mr. Lombardo.
他开头是我的朋友
He was my friend at first.
后来我被抓了… 他却不再保护我…
And then l got busted, and he didn't stick up for me...
而我不得不滚到那个鬼地方去
...and l had to go away to that hell hole.
一开始你是他的最爱，然后却“谁管你?”
lt's like you're his favorite, and then ''Who cares?''
让她停下来
Make her stop.
凯利 说要这么做…
When Kelly said that we should do this...
-…我在想，“真酷.” -凯利!
-...l thought, ''Cool.'' -Kelly!
那些大人物给找我的麻烦，像 杜奎特警官
All these big shots screwing me over, like that cop, Duquette.
-现在他们自己有麻烦了. -对不起，法官大人
-Now they're gonna get screwed. -l'm sorry, Your Honor.
我反对
l have to object.
法官大人，我能讲几句吗?
Your Honor, please, may l be heard?
巴克斯特先生，你不负责这件案子
Mr. Baxter, you are not trying this case.
坐下
Go sit down.
凯利对 伦巴多先生也很恼火
Kelly's pissed at Mr. Lombardo too.
她爱上了他
She's in love with him.
自从她老头死后，他是她的幻想
He's been her fantasy since her old man died.
后来她却发现 伦巴多先生在和她妈干，就这样
Then she found out he was doing her mom, and that was it.
什么? 凯利!
What? Kelly!
你这个臭婊子!
You skanky bitch!
你他妈的把手拿开!你不知道我是谁吗?
Get your fucking hands off of me! Don't you know who l am?
-我准备周一开除你! -就这样
-l'm gonna have you fired on Monday! -Right this way.
拿开这个破东西
Just get the hell away from me.
上帝呀，伙计! 该放松一下啦!
Jesus, man! Let loose!
我在想我住在哪儿
l'm just thinking about where l'm gonna stay.
我的房子没了
l lost my house.
从这该死的恶梦中清醒过来吧
Waking up from a goddamn nightmare.
你就要熬过来了
You'll get over it.
我们给她很重的一记，案子办得无懈可击…
We have got a knockdown, airtight, motherfucker lawsuit...
…给桑德拉・范・赖安
...against Sandra Van Ryan.
也就是这样
Just like that?
这些人毁掉你的生活，兄弟
These people ruined your life, bro.
我跟你说他们太过分.会走过头的!就是没错!
l told you they were gonna go too far. They went overboard! They did!
他们会善后的，相信我. 他们会恳求着安排善后
They'll settle. Believe me. They'll be begging to settle.
哦好啦! 上吧! 等着吧!快点儿，宝贝
Oh, yeah! Here we go! Hey, wait up! Come on, girl.
事情惊人地变化， 萨姆 伦巴多案被驳回…
In a startling turn of events, Sam Lombardo has been dismissed...
他的一个声称的受害者推翻先前的证词
...following a reversal of testimony by one of his alleged victims.
嘿，看这儿
Excuse me. Over here.
嘿.有人看报了吗?
Excuse me. Can anybody read?
嘿! 桑德拉!
Hey! Sandra!
我真想你马上把那讼棍的蛋钉到墙上
l want you to nail that shyster's balls to the nearest wall.
本来是可能的…
We could have, if Ms. Not-So-Bright here...
-…要是那个笨小姐不泽出这些鬼话… -我操
-...hadn't thrown things. -Fuck off.
我都不敢相信你会让他从这个垃圾堆逃出来
l cannot believe you're just gonna let them get away with this shit!
这个最烂的杂种
All on the word of one little white-trash bitch.
我想你还没搞明白，桑迪
l don't think you get it, Sandy.
你的宝贝女儿做了伪证
Your princess here committed perjury.
我所能做的只是让她逃脱他妈的牢狱之灾
lt'll be all l can do to keep her fucking little ass out of jail.
那我们要做什么?
Well, what are we going to do?
- 给你咖啡. - 谢谢你
-You're gonna love this place, Tom. -Thank you.
杰珀・波克・朴莱特会杀了你
That jalapeo pork platter will kill you.
我的意思是:你不能这个星期每天都吃寿司
l mean, you can't eat sushi every day of the week.
宝登，为什么不停下
Bowden, why don't you cut the crap...
…告诉我你的客户究竟需要什么
...and tell me what your client really wants.
好的，巴克斯特
Okay, Baxter.
我的客户希望你的客户戴上马鞍…
My client wants your client to saddle up...
…然后我们骑在他的屁股上面直奔银行
...so we can ride her ass straight to the bank.
你知道的，肯
You know, Ken.
我可以叫你 肯么?
May l call you Ken?
另外的案件，另外的时间
There will be other cases, other days.
我明白…
The way l see it...
汤米
...Tommy...
…今天所有人都吃屎了吗?
...is that everybody's gotta eat some shit sometime.
你要热的么?
You like yours hot?
是的
Yeah.
- 给你咖啡，萨姆. - 谢谢你
-Here's your coffee, Sam. -Thank you.
肯
Ken.
对不起我晚了
Sorry l'm late.
替我接一下电话，勒诺
Hold my calls, Lenore.
好的，宝登先生
Okay, Mr. Bowden.
谢谢你，桑德拉
Thank you, Sandra.
我会找你的
l'll be seeing you.
- 怎么样? - 好啊. 来吧
-Okay? -Okay. Yeah.
很高兴见到你，汤姆
Nice to see you, Tom.
一起来吧 午餐
Come by. We'll have lunch.
俱乐部见
See you at the club.
俱乐部见，汤米!
See you at the club, Tommy!
嘿，汤米，今天战绩如何，朋友?
Hey, Tom. What did you shoot today, pal?
嘿，我说伙计!
Hey, my man!
这是给你的
This is for you.
-你做的很棒，肯. -是的
-You did good, Ken. -Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
我知道你宁愿什么事都没发生…但它发生了…
l know there's a part of you that wishes none of this had happened, but it did.
那就拿着这钱好好享受一下
So take the money and enjoy yourself.
怎么样?找个好地方
All right? Find a happy place.
勒诺，送伦巴多先生出去好吗?
Lenore, would you see Mr. Lombardo out, please?
-再见，萨姆. -再见，勒诺
-Goodbye, Sam. -Bye, Lenore.
照看好我的蜥蜴，好吗?
Take care of my lizards?
你好，凯利
Hello, Kelly.
去死吧
Drop dead.
你知道我妈妈付给你什么了?我的信托基金
You know how my mom's paying you off? She's breaking my trust.
她死前我动不到这些钱，但现在她赔给你
l can't touch it until she's dead, and now she's breaking it to pay you.
对不起，凯利
l'm sorry, Kelly.
为什么你不再去干她啊 !你们可以一起花这钱
Why don't you start fucking her again! You can spend it together!
我他妈的恨死你了，你这个杂种!
l hate you! l fucking hate you, you son of a bitch!
我恨死你了!
l fucking hate you!
你看，阿蒂?我不能再回来了，即使我想回来
You see, Art? l couldn't come back even if l wanted to.
可恶的女佣
Goddamn maid.
那么你拿到了我妈妈的钱
So you got my mom's money.
多少?
How much?
你知道有多少
You know how much.
那该你付帐了
Your turn to pay.
成功了! 我们干掉这个婊子啦!
lt worked! We screwed the bitch!
说的对
lt worked just like you said.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
你他妈的把我吓坏啦.你不该来这儿.就这个
You scared the shit out of me. What's wrong is your coming here.
你他妈的疯了吗?
That's what's wrong. Are you fucking crazy?
是的，我是疯了… 去问问我妈妈
Yeah, l'm crazy. Ask my mom.
那么，8百50万元分成三份是多少呢?
So how much is 8.5 million divided by three?
哦，很好
Oh, great. Yeah, this is a big joke. Big joke.
都觉得很好笑吗.你们真他妈的认为这事完了吗?
Everyone thinks this is really funny. Do you think this is fucking over?
我告诉你们.还早着呢
Let me tell you something. lt's a long fucking way from over.
我是认真的
l'm serious.
今晚以后，我们三个不能再被人看到在一起
After tonight the three of us are not to be seen together again.
今晚以后?
After tonight?
是的，好了
Yeah, well...
…我们都在这儿了，不是吗?
...we're here, aren't we?
也许庆祝一下也不错…
So maybe one celebration is okay...
如果我们达成一致的话…
...if we're in agreement...
那么从现在…
...that from here on out...
你们就要完全照我说的做
...you do exactly as l say.
法律辅导员总是很会找乐子
Guidance counselors get to find out all sorts of interesting things.
现在我要你们两个接吻
Now l want you two to kiss.
来吧
Come on, now.
别为这事吵一天
Never let the sun go down on an argument.
我告诉过你，他们把我们当傻瓜玩
l told you they were gonna make us look stupid.
你说的没错.他们的确把我们当傻瓜
Hey, you're right. They did make us look stupid.
你错在不知为什么
What you're wrong about is why.
听听我的看法
All right, hear me out.
伦巴多跟桑德拉・范・赖安之间有一腿，是吗?
Lombardo was having an affair with Sandra Van Ryan, right?
为什么他不告诉我们?
Why not tell us about it?
要是 凯利编造的这故事这正好是个动机
That's a hell of a motive for Kelly to fabricate this story.
也许伦巴多的律师在法庭上留这一手
Maybe Lombardo's attorney was saving the affair for the trial.
我想过这些事，然后说:你是伦巴多.你已完蛋了
l thought about it and said: ''You're Lombardo. Your life is trashed.
你又不想在监狱里熬三个月，除非--
You don't wanna sit in jail for three months unless--''
除非什么?
Unless what?
除非你设计要桑德拉・范・赖安跟你在哪天结一个大帐
Unless you're setting Sandra Van Ryan up for the big payday.
在整个这事发生前，伦巴多已经债务缠身
Lombardo was eyeball-deep in debt before this whole thing started...
…要想继续维持芭芭拉巴克斯特那样昂贵的讲究的生活
...trying to keep up with a pricey girl like Barbara Baxter. That's expensive.
伦巴多 可能会破产，但为什么 凯利要偷这个钱?
Lombardo may be broke, but why would Kelly steal?
这小子拿到的这笔钱是她祖父留下的，而她在她母亲去世前是不能碰它们的
Kid's got money from her grandfather she can't touch until her mother dies.
我来告诉你，这个小子本想跟有钱人结婚
l'm telling you, this guy wanted to marry money.
当这些不能实现… 他就去在这两个女孩身上下工夫…
When that didn't happen, he went to work on these two girls...
…利用她们去算计桑德拉・范・赖安
...using them to set up Sandra Van Ryan.
我告诉你， 他当我们是白痴搭档.
I'm telling you, they chumped us, partner.
他们从一开始就把我们当木头.
They chumped us right from the start.
游得不错
Nice stroke.
你来这里有什么原因吗?
ls there some reason why you're here?
-我想，是好奇. -好奇什么?
-Curiosity, l guess. -About what?
怎么提高你的蛙泳水平?
How to improve your breast stroke?
我好奇的是在你看来你和萨姆，苏西三个人以后会怎样?
No. l want to know how you see things working out for you, Sam and Suzie.
什么意思?
Excuse me?
你们三人是想要一起到加勒比海…
You three gonna go to the Caribbean together?
从此以后过快乐生活?
Live happily ever after?
问题是三人组合很少能一直合作下去
You see, the thing about it is that threesomes rarely work out.
你丫神经病吧
You're out of your mind.
要一个人保守秘密已经很难 别提三个啦
lt's hard enough for one person to keep a secret, let alone three.
特别是当其中两人相爱时
Especially when two of them are in love.
既然得到那些钱，你和萨姆可不想边上有个吸毒的
You and Sam don't want that pill-head around now that you have the money.
…我说的没错吧?
Am l right?
萨姆干掉苏西前会不会跟你说一下?
Sam sell you on the idea right up front of whacking Suzie? Hey!
那会是谋杀，孩子
That's murder, kid.
上帝啊，警官，省省吧
Police. God, get a life.
你觉得很好?
You're good, you know that?
但你是不是不曾想过那个怪诞的苏西家会成为一个阻碍?
But you don't think that little freak Suzie's gonna hold up, do you?
你好.，苏西
Hello, Suzie.
你最好别再碰那该死的东西
You better watch it with that shit.
你又出事啦，这是第二次
You get busted again, you go back in a two-time loser.
没错，大不了去死
Yeah, or wind up dead.
你知道…
You know...
我想我从未告诉过你，我对你朋友的事感到有多抱歉
...l don't think l ever told you how sorry l was about your friend.
他叫什么?
What was his name?
苏西.你记得他名字的.告诉我
Come on, help me out here, Suzie. You know his name.
-大卫. -是的.没错. 大卫
-Davy. -Yeah. That's right. Davy.
我真的对那事情感到抱歉
l was sorry about the way that worked out.
- 那都是你们警察的废话. - 你说什么?
-That is cop bullshit. -What was that? What was that?
我再也不用听这些 你再也别想压着我
l don't have to listen to this. You can't shove me around.
-我现在有朋友了. -嘿!
-l have friends now. -Hey!
这是雷，苏西. 你别想糊弄过去!
This is Ray, Suzie. You don't have shit!
你从来就混不过去， 你以后也混不掉
You never had shit and you never will have shit.
看看这个
Take a look at this.
看看.它不会咬你的
Go ahead, take it. lt's not gonna bite you.
拿着!
Take it!
你的朋友萨姆存的支票
Your friend Sam deposited the check.
他把钱转到一个离岸帐户，一个数字帐号
He transferred the funds to a numbered offshore account.
警局甚至不知道帐户的名字是谁.想想其中有一个名字会是你吗?
Cops don't know the names on it. Think one of them is yours?
他为一个小岛付下定金，而且分期付款买一艘游艇
He also put a down payment on island property and a lease on a sailboat.
你要去出海，是吗?
You're into sailing, aren't you?
我不知道你为什么要告诉我这些，为什么要来这儿?
l don't know why you're telling me this. Why are you here?
我告诉你是因为我完全知道将要发生的事
l'm telling you this because l know exactly what's going on.
两个人可以成为伙伴， 三个人就多余了
Two's company. Three's a crowd.
现在相信我
Come on, now.
你也不认为凯利和萨姆 会和你一起分这笔钱吧?
You don't think Kelly and Sam are gonna share that money with you.
让我单独呆会儿
Leave me alone.
你要知道
You know...
你要知道，如果我是你，我就希望我现在脑子清醒点儿…
...l'd want a clear head right now if l were you...
这样我就能看清楚我的新朋友
...so l could keep a real close eye on my new friends.
我不愿看到你的结局那么惨…
l'd hate to see you come to a bad end...
…就像 大卫一样
...like Davy.
真见鬼
Oh, shit.
我是萨姆 伦巴多. 请在哔声后留言.
You've reached Sam Lombardo. Wait for the beep, leave a message.
我真不能相信你竟会给萨姆打电话.你到底怎么了?
l can't believe you called Sam. What's the matter with you?
我很害怕，我不知道该相信谁
l'm scared there's no one to trust.
你可以相信我
You can trust me.
喂?
Hello?
-凯利，苏西在你这儿? - 是的
-Kelly, is Suzie there? -Yeah.
我正担心这个.
Christ, l was afraid of that.
她给我留下个蠢话
She left this insane message.
一边抽着那些东西
Between whatever she's been smoking out there...
…一边是这他妈的警察.她真会搞砸掉.
...and this fucking cop, she's gonna blow it.
让这婊子冷静下来.
Calm the bitch down.
为什么你不能来，求你？
Why can't you come? Please?
萨姆，我真的好想你
Sam, l miss you so much.
我也想你，凯利，但是现在不行.
l miss you too, Kelly, but l can't right now.
我们要完成计划，好吗?
We gotta stick to the plan, okay?
如果他妈的她不能挺住--….
If she can't get a fucking grip....
- 那怎么样? - 你知道怎样.
-Then what? -You know what.
我会亲自处理的
I'll handle it.
但我需要你，凯利.我要你今晚为我呆在那儿.
But l need you, Kelly. l need you to be there for me tonight.
- 好吧. - 很好.
-Okay. -Good.
这才是我的好姑娘.你很坚强，知道吗?
That's my girl. You're the strong one, you know that?
现在叫苏西也来听. 我想要你们两个都听着.
Now, put Suzie on the line. I want you both to hear this.
苏西.
Suzie.
萨姆?
Sam?
现在，听着…
Now, look...
…我们要冷静下来，我们每个人…
...we gotta stay calm, all of us.
现在，这事以后，人们都认为我很有钱了…
Now, since the settlement, people think l'm rich...
…所以我要出去大把花钱，做那些富人该做的事.
...so l'm out there spending money, doing what rich guys do.
可这个警察，他想要他妈的添乱 不能让他得逞.
This cop, Duquette, he's gonna try and fuck with you. Don't let him.
- 你说起来容易. -苏西，别崩溃.
-Yeah, that's easy for you to say. -Suzie, don't fall apart.
能让这事穿帮的，只有我们自己
The only people who can fuck this up is us.
你们--你们想要甩掉我，是不是?
You are gonna fuck me over, aren't you?
去你的.
Oh, for chrissake.
就是!
You are!
你是低能啊，还是脑袋被沼气熏昏啦?
Are you retarded, or just brain-dead from whiffing fumes out in the swamp?
我也正想这么说你--满脑子泥浆，就像我妈妈一样.
That's what l am to you, isn't it? Swamp trash, just like my mom.
别碰我!
Don't!
你个瓜批!
You stupid cunt!
你很害怕，是吗?
You are scared, aren't you?
上帝啊!
Ray! Jesus Christ!
- 你疯了? - 你听她在叫“萨姆”
-Are you crazy? -Hear her say ''Sam''?
它们在和 伦巴多通电话.你看这两个女孩
That was Lombardo on the phone. And you saw the two girls.
磁带上的谈话莫名其妙
The conversation on the tape is unintelligible.
我们现在有的只是你在范・赖安 的私人产业上
What we have here is you on the Van Ryan property...
- 拍到的色情镜头! - 我真不能相信
-...shooting a porn flick! -l can't believe this.
一个月前，这两个女孩还在法庭上大打出手
A month ago, they threw things at each other in court.
她们在演戏! 他们都在演戏!
They were acting! They were all acting!
我们却相信它，深陷其中
We bought it, hook, line and sinker.
现在他们要带着桑德拉・范・赖安的8百万美金逃跑
They're getting away with $8 million from Sandra Van Ryan.
她想保住的那些钱，她没有计划去毁掉这个男人的生活
She might have saved it if she didn't try to ruin him.
如果你认为那小子强奸你的女儿，你还会去追求他?
You wouldn't go after a guy you thought raped your daughter?
她也像我们一样相信了那些鬼话!
She bought the same goddamn story we did!
你们两个听着，你们不是在办一个案子，因为现在没有他妈的案子
Both of you, you're not on a case, because there is no fucking case!
我很清楚桑德拉・范・赖安这个人，如果你继续这样在她家周围晃来晃去…
l've had it with Sandra Van Ryan, and you keep mucking around...
…那她一定会去控告我们非法侵入
...and she's gonna sue us for invasion of privacy.
所以不要理这些人的事! 嘿! 雷!
So get out of these people's lives! Hey! Ray!
- 我说清楚啦? - 你觉得这只是涉及到钱?
-Hey! Am l getting through? -You think this is just about money?
大概我们看起来很蠢?问问这个人吧
About us looking stupid? Question him.
你会发现有个变态狂在背后控制，那些女孩将会走向死路
You'll find a manipulative psychopath, and those girls will wind up dead.
给这个蠢货一点事去做吧
Give him something to do.
- 也许该让他去调查肯尼迪的谋杀案. - 我明白
-Look into the Kennedy assassination. -l understand.
下次这个混蛋…
Next time this fucking piece of shit...
再在这儿拖住我，我会去控告你
...drags me down here, l'm gonna sue you.
这次你混蛋够运，我最后一次放过你
You're goddamn lucky l didn't sue last time.
- 我明白. - 我现在可以走啦?
-l agree. -Am l free to go?
- 是的. - 谢谢
-Yes. -Thank you.
- 操蛋 - 你说什么?
-Cocksucker. -Yeah, what was that?
- 你听见啦，傻 - 你敢当我面再说一遍?
-You heard me, motherfucker. -Yeah, you wanna say that to my face?
你看什么呢?
What are you looking at?
- 我猜我可能会被调离这里. - 可以这么说
-l guess l kind of lost it out there. -You could say that.
你有过这样的事?你明知道有些事会发生…
Were you ever in a situation where you saw something coming...
…而你可以阻止的，却不去做你该做的
...and you didn't do what you could to stop it?
我们都有此经历
We all have.
我是说你看到一件坏事，然后它发生了…
l mean something bad that you saw coming, and then it happened...
可你却什么都不能做，而且--
...and you-- You didn't do anything, and....
我遇到过一次
l did that once.
我不想再来一次
l don't wanna do it again.
我还以为我们要去看电影
l thought we were going to a movie.
我想我们只是需要打发时间
l think we just need to get wasted.
快来
Yeah.
Come on.
我希望有一天我能住在海边
l wanna live at the beach someday.
噢，糟糕
Oh, shit.
我忘了钥匙
l left the keys.
我去拿
l'll get them.
凯利?
Kelly?
苏西
Suzie.
是我
lt's me.
我很担心你，所以我决定…
l was worried about you, and l decided...
在分手之前，我们三个应该再聚最后一次
...the three of us should get together one last time before we split up.
-你对我很生气吗? -不.不
-Are you mad at me? -No, no.
我也许应该多告诉你一些关于…
l probably should've told you a bit more about...
…我准备要演的角色
...the part l intended to play.
但我们今晚要来一次
But we'll go through it again tonight.
庆祝一下，而不是自杀约会
This is a celebration, Suzie, not a suicide pact.
我们要凉快一下只要放松一点…
We're gonna chill out and just relax...
…来一点儿香槟…
...have a little champagne...
…看看星星…
...watch the stars....
凯利?
Kelly?
在你妈妈的车后备箱里找到毯子啦?
You got a blanket in the back of your mom's Rover?
行行好，再去帮我们拿来?
Why don't you be an angel and run over and get it for us?
好姑娘
Good girl.
给你说说我为我们精心挑选的这条船
Let me tell you about the boat l picked out for us.
你还好?
You okay?
要是我妈知道我开走她的车，她会杀了我的
My mom would kill me if she knew l took the Rover.
四轮?
Been four-wheeling?
-离开我的屋子! -我没在你的屋子里面
-Get off my property! -l'm not on your property.
-如果你不离开这里-- -你要报警么?我就是警察!
-lf you don't get out of here-- -You'll call a cop? l am a cop!
我操!
Goddamn it!
你是说她昨晚没回家
So you say she didn't come home last night.
她是一直说要去洛杉玑，但她的衣服全都在这里
She's been talking about going to L.A., but her clothes are all still here.
沃尔特! 你有病啊，它们用得好好的
Walter! You get sick, it'll serve you right.
找些倒在路上的老流浪汉的的牙齿
Found some teeth in an old trailer down the road.
他说他们很合适
He says they'll fit.
审判结束后，苏西就没回学校
Suzie hasn't been back to school since the trial.
哦，现在他们肯定在说她不能毕业
Oh, and now they're saying that she can't graduate.
这都是 凯利 范・赖安带她陷进去的，你们都知道
lt is that Kelly Van Ryan that got her into this whole mess, and you know it.
我们会查的，鲁比
Well, we'll look into it for you, Ruby.
如果我们发现什么，你会第一个知道
We find something, you'll be the first to know.
走啦
Come on.
现在开始啦，格洛里亚. 这就是开始
lt's starting, Gloria. This is how it begins.
我们根本不知道什么. 她也许在别的任何地方
Ray, we don't know anything yet. She could be anywhere.
我会在警局放下你， 打电话查一下苏西的车
l'll drop you off. Put a call out on Suzie's car.
你要去什么地方吗?
You got someplace you wanna be?
-你有约会? -你只要帮我查出这辆车
-You got a date? -Just check the car out for me.
在那艘旧船那儿
lt's over here, by that old boat.
那你和苏西来过这儿?
So you and Suzie used to come out here together?
是的，有时候
Yeah, sometimes.
有许多小子都来这儿
A lot of the kids hang out here.
你真得觉得苏西出事啦?
You really think something bad happened to Suzie?
伦巴多来过这里?
Lombardo ever come out here?
我说了什么好笑的事?
l say something funny?
不是，我只是说，这样想 伦巴多先生也太 --
No, but l mean, just the idea that Mr. Lombardo would--
好吧，我听到一些，他和孩子们的关系不错
Well, the way l heard it, he was pretty tight with the kids.
你和他是朋友对吧?
You and him were pals, right?
是的，是他让我来航行组的
Yeah, but he got me onto the sailing team.
告诉我说我可以靠自己的努力完成学业，就像他那样
Told me l could work my way through college, like he did.
萨姆 伦巴多 是靠体育奖学金上的迈阿密大学…
Sam Lombardo went to the University of Miami on an athletic scholarship.
这些船可跟这该死的事无关
Boats didn't have a damn thing to do with it.
我会在这里呆一会儿，孩子
Listen, l'm gonna be here a while, kid.
你去高速公路上赶公共汽车吧?
Why don't you go up to the highway and catch the bus?
嘿，吉米
Hey, Jimmy.
人并不总像他外表的那样. 记住这句话
People aren't always what they appear to be. Don't forget that.
- 这就是作案现场. - 尸体在哪儿?
-This is where they did it. -Where's the body?
在沼泽里，很可能 这小子是个沼鼠
The swamp, most likely. Guy's a swamp rat.
他知道在这里尸体不会被发现， 但他犯了一个错误
He knows it won't be found, but he made a mistake.
她祖母说过她感到很危险，所以想跑掉…
She'd been threatening to run away and l found the car at the bus terminal.
你不认为是山姆把它停在那里的?我在公共汽车总站发现她的汽车
You don't think Sam put it there?
稍等一下. 格洛里亚，给那辆车喷点灰取印模
Hold on a second. Gloria, have the car dusted for prints.
如果苏西真的被谋杀， 一定是那个范・赖安 小混蛋干的
And if Suzie even was murdered, it was that damn Van Ryan kid.
一个小叛逆从一开始就注定啦
Little sociopath's the one who started this.
- 我们多长时间可以拿到结果? - 我们可以立刻拿到血型的报告
-How long till we get something? -We can get blood type now.
核对牙齿记录时间要长些. DNA的测试结果要几个星期
Dental records will take longer. DNA could take weeks.
可怜的笨苏西. 从来不曾有过机会
Poor, dumb Suzie. Kid never had a chance.
- 我们还不知道什么. - 让我告诉你，凯利 就是下一个
-We don't know that. -l'm telling you, Kelly's next.
让我来告诉你，离开这里… 马上
l'm telling you, you get off this right now.
别他妈的让我听到你再去打扰伦巴多
Don't even fucking let me hear about you bothering Lombardo.
大卫
David!
你拿到身份报告，直接通知我!
You get an lD, you call me!
帮我一个忙好不好?
Will you do me a favor?
雷，你听到他说的
Ray, you heard him.
他只是说让我不要碰伦巴多， 关于你他倒是什么都没说
He told me to stay away. He didn't say anything about you.
想想如果我正确而亨特错怎样
What if l'm right and Hunter's wrong?
求你，这次你得帮我
Please, you gotta help me out on this, partner.
如果这牙齿不是苏西的， 你得放弃这想法?
And if the teeth aren't Suzie's, you'll give this up?
如果这次我错，我听你的
lf l'm wrong about those teeth, you got my word.
-喂? -我给你你打过电话.
-Hello? -I've been calling you.
-我想见你. -你在哪儿?
-l wanna see you. -Where are you?
-这该死的客人房 -好的.呆在那儿.
-The stupid guest house. -Good. Stay there.
萨姆，我真的很紧张
Sam, l'm really nervous.
凯利，放松点
Kelly, relax.
吃一片你妈妈的镇静药什么的
Take one of your mom's Valiums or something.
一个星期后，当你乘上飞机， 这些就结束了.我们就有钱啦
ln a week, you get on the plane, this is over. We're rich.
但是如果他们发现了呢?
But what if they find out?
上帝，他们会把你推上电椅
My God, they'd put you in the electric chair.
听着，凯利…
Look, Kelly...
…今晚呆在那里，想想毕业舞会
...stay in the guest house, skip the graduation parties.
我非常爱你
l love you so much.
我也爱你，凯利.
And I love you too, Kelly.
做个好姑娘 呆在那儿.
Be a good girl and stay where you are.
在别人的窗户外面偷窥…
Peeping in people's windows?
…是不是违法的?
lsn't that against the law?
苏西・托乐 失踪了
Suzie Toller's missing.
- 什么时候? - 她昨晚没有回家
-Since when? -She didn't come home last night.
我们在公共汽车终点站发现她的汽车
We found her car at the bus terminal.
雷 认为她已被害
Ray thinks she was murdered.
我不知道该说什么
Well, l don't know what to tell you.
你可以告诉我你昨晚在哪儿
You could tell me where you were last night.
我想我能告诉你， 但我真得没必要这么做，是不是?
l suppose l could, but l don't really have to, now, do l?
来这儿
Come here.
我给你看样东西
l wanna show you something.
看起来像是准备离开
Looks like goodbye.
凯利的档案
Kelly's file.
读读看. 你会发现这是个愤怒的，性困惑的女孩…
Read it. You're gonna find an angry, sexually confused girl...
…至少有两个人使得她对生活产生恐惧
...who threatened the lives of at least two people.
哪两个人?
What two people?
其中一个是她母亲
One of them was her mother.
另一个是…
The other one was...
…她的一个女同学…
...a female classmate...
…和她可能有些复杂的性关系
...she may have been sexually involved with.
苏西?
Suzie?
现在你拿着这个档案
Now you got the file.
看看它
Read it.
我想它会让你对此事有新的看法
l think it'll give you a new perspective on things.
为什么你在审讯前不告诉我们这些?
Why didn't you tell us about this before the trial?
因为那时我还有些个人守则
Because then l had principles.
对我来说很重要的
That meant a lot to me.
但现在…
Now...
…我不再在乎
...l don't care.
我也许应该走
l should probably go now.
除非你打算找些什么事留住我
Unless you're planning on holding me for something.
-杜奎特.发生什么事? -我很累.我回家啦.
-Duquette. What's happening? -I'm tired. I'm going home.
-伦巴多在哪? -走了…
-Where's Lombardo? -He's gone.
日，格洛里亚，岩石上的血型跟苏西吻合
Goddamn it, Gloria, the blood type on the rocks matches Suzie's.
我来告诉你一些事情，雷:
Let me tell you something, Ray:
关于这件事，有许多是你不清楚的
There's more to this story than you know.
如果苏西死掉了…
If Suzie is dead...
…亨特 可能要盯上 凯利.
...Hunter may be on the right track about Kelly.
雷?
Ray?
混蛋，雷
Shit, Ray.
-是谁? -杜奎特侦探
-Who is it? -lt's Detective Duquette.
开门
Open the gate, now.
-你好，凯利. -你来这儿干什么?
-Hello, Kelly. -What are you doing here?
哪里--? 凯利! 凯利!
Where's--? Kelly! Kelly!
我只是刚一转眼，也就一眨眼的时间
l just looked away for a second, just a split second.
就是那样-- 就来啦--
And just like that, bingo...
…她用膝盖顶我的腹股沟
...she put a knee in my groin.
我开始没倒下，慢慢地往下-----
l didn't go down, but it slowed me down...
…就这样
...just enough.
我碰不到她
l couldn't get to her.
她拿把枪对着我
She turned on me with the gun.
开一枪
Fired one shot.
我躲一下打中肩膀
l took the hit in the shoulder.
我没别的选择
l had no choice.
只能开枪还击
l had to return fire.
两枪，我想是，打中胸部
Two rounds, l think, in the chest.
我去那儿是想保护她的
l went there to protect her.
我--我去那儿是想保护她的
l went-- l went there to protect her.
杜奎特侦探
Detective Duquette.
我曾在军事情报局干过一段时间， 在那儿我们有个说法:
l spent time in military intelligence, and we had a saying there:
一次是偶然. 两次是巧合
''Once is happenstance. Twice is coincidence.
三次是敌意
Three times is enemy action.''
你现在已经两次，杜奎特…
This is twice for you, Duquette...
所以我不想看到第三次
...and l intend to see to it that there is no third time.
我们调查认为你打的很准， 这个有点无关紧要
Our investigation finds that this was a good shooting, but that's irrelevant.
但你忽视上级的指示
You ignored the advice of your superiors.
从而，造成两个年轻女孩的死亡
Consequently, two young women are dead.
从现在开始，你被停职. 同时终止你的养老金和福利金
You are, as of now, terminated, with forfeiture of pension and benefits.
勾赛尔局长…
Chief Goodsall...
…杜奎特侦探发现 苏珊・玛丽・托乐的牙齿和血迹…
...Detective Duquette found Susan Marie Toller's teeth and blood...
就在被叫做碎石海滩的地方
...near the area known as Stoner Beach.
越野车里也发现托乐的血迹
Miss Toller's blood was also found in the Van Ryan Range Rover.
这让警方认为…
This has led this office to conclude...
苏珊・玛丽・托乐 是被 凯利・拉尼尔・范・赖安谋杀的
...that Susan Marie Toller was murdered by Kelly Lanier Van Ryan.
她- 她没有
She-- She didn't.
杜奎特先生
Mr. Duquette.
调查结束 你可以走啦
This investigation is concluded. You're dismissed.
谢谢你，保罗
Thank you, Paul.
你好啊，搭档
Howdy, partner.
上帝啊，你这家伙.我还以为你明天来
Jesus, man. l wasn't expecting you until tomorrow.
看，你的好女友打的
Hey, nice girlfriend you got there.
凯利本来只是要当个顶罪的
Kelly was only supposed to be framed.
这婊子开枪打我
The bitch shot me.
该死，你是个警察. 难道他们没有教你让人解除武器?
Shit, you're a cop. Don't they teach you to disarm people?
你知道 打腿或者类似地方?
You know, shoot them in the leg or something?
你忽然有点多愁善感啊
Did you become squeamish about this stuff before or after...
…是在你用葡萄酒瓶当敲死小苏西之前还是之后?
...you bludgeoned little Suzie to death with a wine bottle?
我们没有安排凯利 死掉，雷. 这不是计划里的
Kelly wasn't supposed to die, Ray. lt wasn't part of the plan.
伙计，事情也不会更好啦. 他们相信是凯利谋杀的苏西
lt couldn't have worked out better. They're convinced Kelly killed Suzie.
我不能告诉他们实情
l couldn't talk them out of it.
我只想告诉你，我不喜欢意外
l'm telling you, l don't like surprises.
你应该这样看这件事:每朵乌云都有金边
Look at it this way: Every cloud has a silver lining.
现在再不会有破绽
Now there's no loose ends.
明天来，你就再也别看到我
Come tomorrow, you'll never see me again.
好吧，听听看，要明天
Oh, listen, about tomorrow...
…我已经对银行讲过但他们说， 需要两个工作日…
...l spoke to the bank and they said it's gonna take two working days...
…来完成转帐，所以--
...to make the transfer, so....
-胡说 -哦，是的
-Bullshit. -Oh, yeah.
你可以自己打电话
Call them yourself.
不管怎样，还急啥呢? 等个一两天
Anyway, what's your hurry? Kick back for a day or two.
我们驾船出海吧. 我刚把船装配好
We'll take out the boat. l just had it outfitted.
我也许还需要个水手
l could use a deck hand.
这是两个大笔的银行帐户
Here's to large bank accounts.
你应该轻松一下，伙伴. 你是个富人了
You gotta lighten up, partner. You're a rich man.
两个大笔的帐户，而且毫无破绽
To large accounts and no loose ends.
毫无破绽
And no loose ends.
嘿，雷，看见那个绞盘啦?
Hey, Ray, you see that winch?
拿这个工具去拧一下. 船要全速向风
Take a couple turns on it. She's luffing.
- 你是说那个东西? - 没错. 雷
-You mean that thing? -Yeah, Ray.
我们管它叫绞盘，用它来拉紧船帆
We call it a winch. lt's what we use to tighten the sails.
- 那为什么不开始干呢? - 我们把这看成一个假期呀
-So why don't you start cranking? -This is supposed to be a vacation.
为什么你不去弄艘好的机动船呢?
Why don't you get a nice powerboat?
来啊，雷. 我会让你成为一个真正的水手的
Come on, Ray. l'll make a sailor out of you yet.
或者让我淹死
Or get me drowned.
它锈住啦
lt's stuck.
你说什么?锈住? 稍微用点儿力吧
What do you mean, it's stuck? Put a little elbow grease in it.
锈住啦，我告诉过你
lt's stuck, l'm telling you.
得把帆脚索绑在什么东西上
The jenny sheet must be caught on something.
那你去右舷看看你是否能把它解下来?
Why don't you go starboard and see if you can unhook it?
- 你说的我一句也听不懂. - 好吧，雷
-l don't understand a word you said. -Okay, Ray.
你看见那根绳子? 看看它下头…
You see this line right here? Follow it down...
看看它是否被什么缠住
...and see if you can see what it's snagged on.
你会害死我
You're killing me.
-这个东西? -就是它.就在那儿
-You mean this thing? -That's it. That one right there.
看到东西了么?
You see anything?
再向下看一点儿
Look a little lower.
就这样
That's it.
我忘告诉你，雷:
Guess l forgot to tell you, Ray:
一只手管船， 一只手管自己
One hand for the boat, the other one for yourself.
航海的第一准则
First rule of sailing.
雷!
Ray!
-怎样啦? -很不错啊，操他奶奶的
-What happened? -Nice try, motherfucker!
是你!
You!
你已经死啦
You're dead!
不，我没死
No, l'm not.
萨姆
Sam.
-萨姆，该死的! -对不起，搭档
-Sam, for chrissake! -Sorry, partner.
你真的不该杀凯利
You really shouldn't have killed Kelly.
你也不该在那片沼泽地里杀死那个孩子
You shouldn't have killed that kid out in the glades either.
-他的名字? -大卫
-What was his name? -Davy.
那是我儿子沃尔特，沃尔特
That's my son, Walter.
他做这工作很久，所以你们不用害怕. 请吧，请进
He's been doing this a long time, so don't be afraid. Please, come on in.
谢谢光临沼泽地
Thank you so much for coming down to the glades.
你是来这里看沃尔特表演的，还是公事?
Did you come here to watch Walter, or is this an official visit?
不，事实上，今天我休息
No. Actually, it's my day off.
我觉得你看起来不大一样
l thought you looked different.
我来这儿是因为我希望你能跟我说说
l came because l was hoping you would talk to me.
关于苏西?
About Suzie?
事实上，我希望你能说说雷 杜奎特
Actually, l was wondering if you would talk to me about Ray Duquette.
他过去常来这里
He used to come around here.
他跟其中的一个女孩有些关系--
He had a thing going with one of the girls--
沼泽地周围这些女孩
Girls. Over at the glades.
从我听到的好像是跟她鬼混
Got sort of hung up on her, from what l hear.
- 她仍在那儿工作? - 从那晚以后就没有
-She still work there? -Not after that night.
我只知道，第二天早上…
All l know is, the next morning...
她离开，但一个男孩死啦
...she was gone and a boy was dead.
是个塞米诺尔族人，名字叫大卫. 他迷上雷的婊子
Seminole kid named Davy. He had a crush on Ray's whore.
他看到雷抽她，他想管一档
Caught Ray slapping her around, and he tried to stop it.
所以雷把他杀啦
So Ray killed him.
苏西 看到
Suzie saw it.
所以他逮捕她，然后又保释她
So he busted her and sent her up.
你知道那仅仅为证明他有这个能力
You know, just to prove that he could.
雷 杜奎特就是这样的
That's all there is to say about Ray Duquette.
为雷
To Ray.
我们赢啦萨姆，现在结束啦
We won. Sam, it's over.
像个妄想狂 看看我们周围，萨姆
Wow. Talk about paranoid. Take a look around us, Sam.
即使我要除掉你，你也要先教会我操纵这船啊
You're gonna have to teach me how to drive this before l can get rid of you.
好吧，托乐
Okay, Toller.
我想整好船帆. 抓住那个绞盘
l wanna trim the sail. Grab a hold of that winch.
-去它的绞盘.我想要驾驶. -不是那样的
-Fuck the winch. l wanna drive. -lt doesn't work that way.
你不是驾驶它，你要使它扬帆航行
You don't drive it, you sail it.
现在去抓住绞盘
Now, get on that winch.
我想要巡航一会儿
l just wanna cruise for a while.
这很有意思. 这是我注意到你的第一件事，萨姆
That's funny. That's one of the first things l noticed about you, Sam.
你喜欢巡航
You like to cruise.
-苏西. -拿大学期间举个例子
-Suzie. -Take college, for instance.
我打赌你在那儿选修的课程都是多项选择的结果
l bet the classes you took were ones where the finals were multiple choice.
而且你从不买书. 你只是寻找一个女孩…
And you never bought the book. You'd find a girl to loan you hers.
她把书借给你，然后你跟她上床，对不对?
And then, of course, you'd have to fuck her after that, right?
是这样度过的?
ls that how it went?
是的
Yeah.
好吧，我现在有个测试题来问你
Well, l've got a good pop quiz for you.
当然也是多重选择
Multiple choice, of course.
在驾船逃向赫利俄斯之前…
Before sailing on the Helios...
…美狄亚杀死克瑞翁王和公主… 用的是什么?
...Medea killed King Creon and the princess with what?
一块石头…
A rock?
一把长矛，还是…
A spear gun?
一点儿毒药?
Or a little poison?
毒药!
Poison!
猜的好
Good guess.
范・赖安老了
Van Ryan got old.
他和他的老友会来这里
He and his cronies would come here.
狩猎和嫖娼. 真他妈的狗屎
Hunt and whore. They acted like a bunch of assholes.
一次旅行，他和这个女孩出现了…
One trip, he showed up with this girl...
…他从某地沟上她
...he'd picked up somewhere.
并让他怀孕
Gotten her pregnant.
在沼泽地宰了她
Dumped her in the swamp.
可怜的姑娘死了一年…
Poor girl was dead in a year.
和她一起
That came with her.
小孩呢?
And the child?
在她喝死自己之前已经有了
Well, she had it. Before she drank herself to death.
确实不是个可爱的小孩
Wasn't exactly a love child.
所以你不是她奶奶
So you're not her grandmother.
我培养了他像我一样
l raised her like l was.
但是.不.沃尔特是我唯一的孩子，一个好男孩
But, no. Walt was my only child. He was a good boy.
直到他参军
Until the Army took him.
所以苏西 还有桑德拉・范・赖安算是半个姐妹
So Suzie and Sandra Van Ryan were half sisters.
另一个女孩，凯利? 苏西的外甥女
And the other girl, Kelly? Suzie's niece.
这算是好消息还是坏消息. 我不知道.我们会用信件开始
Well, it may be good news or not. I don't know. We'll start with the letter.
-H. -是的.两个H.
-H. -Yes, there are two H's.
卡车不错啊
Nice truck.
要卖你的船?
Selling your boat?
这个是苏西的船
This was Suzie's boat.
我猜她现在不需要它啦
Guess she won't be needing it now.
真奇怪… 我从未想到苏西会是个水手
Funny. l wouldn't have guessed Suzie was a sailor.
老女人给她做过一次测试 她们说她的智商很高
Old lady had her tested once. They said her lQ was way up there.
大概是200或类似这些玩意
Around 200 or some such shit.
她只要用心可以作好任何事
That girl could do just about anything she put her mind to.
嘿
Hi.
你干什么?
What are you doing out here?
我准备离开
l'm running away.
你认为这样明智么?
You think that's wise?
猜猜还有什么
Guess what else?
我有玩具
l have toys.
我建议一次尝鲜不要去伤害
l suppose one taste won't hurt.
你知道么…
You know...
我被抓住的时候，我给你打过一百次电话
...that weekend l got busted, l called you about a hundred times.
我真的以为你这个废物是我的朋友
l really believed that stuff about you being my friend.
我太天真
Was l naive.
我不知道怎样照的更好:
l can't decide what came out better.
在凯利鼻子上面粘些小草 还是找个狗项圈套在你脖子上
That little straw up Kelly's nose or that dildo shoved up her ass.
你觉得怎样 伦巴多先生?
What do you think, Mr. Lombardo?
看起来好像是你做过同样的事情
Seems to like the same places you do.
-有趣吧，你过去从未见过. -是的，真得有趣
-Funny you never met. -Yeah, real funny.
你知道吗，这点上你想的不对 我会在现场被逮捕
You know, you're wrong about this, and l could get busted on the spot.
信我.这个小子很坏.他喜欢做那些坏事，他爱那些事. 特别是杀死我的那个安排
Trust me. The guy's dirty. He'll love it. Especially the part about killing me.
现在走吧. 去找个新朋友吧
Now, get out of here. Go make yourself a new friend.
你在喝什么呢?
What are you drinking?
我们准备停了.我来了高潮
We gotta stop. l'm gonna come.
从未在沼泽担心你
That never seemed to worry you at the glades.
-不是你的线…. -说你爱我
-That's not your line.... -Say you love me.
我爱你. 给我
l love you. Now, give me the line.
小女孩不会给我高潮的…
No little girl can ever make me come.
你的钳子夹的太紧 你会把这证物弄碎的
You got the pressure too tight. You're gonna crush the evidence.
噢，该死的
Oh, for chrissake.
- 你好，凯利 - 你来这儿干什么?
-Hello, Kelly. -What are you doing here?
可以问你个问题吗，托乐小姐?
May l ask you a question, Ms. Toller?
你喜欢来法庭做客吗?
Did you enjoy being a guest of the state?
我希望我没使你疯狂
l hope l never make you mad.
现金是让你周游世界的
Cash is just walking-around money.
支票是帐户上剩余的钱…
The check is the balance of the numbered account...
…除去留给鲁比  和沃尔特的一百万…
...minus the million we set aside for Ruby and Walter...
…还有一点我的常规收费
...less my usual fee.
案子结束
Case closed.
苏西
Suzie.
好好过
Be good.